Of girls that I never
thought for me.  My boyfriend ordered it
for me today.  Obviously it was a
surprise.  At first I thought I had ordered makeup items from Nykaa.   I have
ordered T-shirts for you.
I too was a little confused after hearing the word T-shirt
until I opened the packet.  Guys these are
inbuilt bra top.  Wow, it feels so
comfortable to wear this.  Only girls can
understand this video.
Aunty has ordered this large size.
I think Excel will probably come out right or
maybe large.  There is some confusion.
But Kaku is so thoughtful, friend.  Friend,
I have ordered this after thinking about all this.
My stomach is churning.
Now look, when I wore the top with proper jeans,
how well it fit compared to the large size.
Last is the blue color which
I have paired with my gym pajamas.
And it looks so good with this too,
man.  This means you can wear them to the gym as well.  The
price of this one T-shirt is ₹1500, at
first it seemed expensive to me too.
But the fabric of the T-shirt and the elastic are of
very good quality.  To me, this
T-shirt felt like velvet on my body.
Now it felt like new clothes had arrived.  Let's go somewhere for a
walk.  Neither is any step pricking me.   The
body is relaxed.  No heaviness, feeling so breathable.  I had a
lot of fun.  I am now going to
check out more products like this on Nykaa.